https://playatgila.com/misc_page/privacy/

PRIVACY
PRIVACY POLICYREVISION DATE: JANUARY 8, 2020At Gila River Casinos (“We”, “Us”, and possessively “Our”), We value your privacy and have posted this Privacy Policy to tell you what information We collect, how We use this information and how We protect it.TESTIMONIALS YOU SEND US ARE NOT SUBJECT TO THIS PRIVACY POLICYIF YOU SEND US INFORMATION REGARDING YOUR EXPERIENCE WITH ONE OR MORE OF OUR PRODUCTS (“YOUR TESTIMONIAL SUBMISSION”), THIS PRIVACY POLICY DOES NOT APPLY TO YOUR TESTIMONIAL SUBMISSION. INSTEAD, PLEASE SEE OUR TERMS OF USE FOR HOW WE MAY USE YOUR TESTIMONIAL SUBMISSION.
INFORMATION WE COLLECT
This Privacy Policy governs with respect to each visitor to our website ("You" and possessively "Your") which is located at www.PlayAtGila.com (the "Website") as well as any other microsite, social media application developed by Gila River Casinos (e.g. Facebook application), and/or any other internet services owned or controlled by Gila River Casinos (the Web Site and all other services shall collectively be referred to as the “Service”).In connection with the Service, Our web servers may automatically recognize and collect Your IP address and, where possible, Your domain name as well as information on which Service pages You access or visit. We may also collect additional non-personally identifiable information, such as pages viewed, browser type, duration and frequency of visits, and other data, and may aggregate any information collected in a manner which does not identify any individual as further described below. Information from You is gathered on Our Service through the use of online forms, site visit data and automatic online collection devices (known as "cookies" or “click-stream data”). Cookies are small bits of text that are either used for the duration of a session ("session cookies") or saved on Your computer's hard drive in order to identify You, or information about You, so Your continuing experience with a website over time can be personalized ("persistent cookies"). Session cookies are automatically deleted when You close Your browser; persistent cookies are stored on Your computer until You delete them. As you use the Internet, a trail of electronic information is left at each website you visit, i.e. “click-stream data”. We may collect and use click-stream data as a form of non-personal information to anonymously determine how much time visitors spend on each page of our Service, how visitors navigate throughout the Service and how we may tailor our web pages to better meet the needs of visitors. All of this non-personal information will be used to improve our Service and our goods and services. Any collection or use of non-personal information including any click-stream data will be anonymous and aggregate, and will not intentionally contain any personally-identifiable information.We do not collect personally identifiable information from You unless You choose to provide it to Us. If You provide Us with Your address or e-mail address, We may use this information to respond to Your message, notify You about updates to Our product offerings, Website, Service, or to contact You for other marketing purposes relating to the products that You requested information about and Our other products or those of our partners or other third parties from time to time. At any time, you may opt-out from receiving any further communications from Us by sending Us an e-mail.
CHILDREN UNDER 21 YEARS OF AGE
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important to Us. For that reason, We do not collect or maintain information from those individuals that We actually know are under 21 years of age, and no part of our Service or advertising has been created or structured to attract anyone under 21 years of age.
WHO HAS ACCESS TO YOUR INFORMATION
WE DO NOT SELL, RENT OR TRANSFER YOUR PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION TO ANYONE. Please note that We reserve the right to and may disclose personally identifiable information about you in response to (a) requests from local, state or federal law enforcement officials; (b) any judicial, administrative or similar proceeding or order, such as subpoena; (c) if required by law; or (d) to investigate suspected fraud, harassment, physical threats, or other violations of any law, rule or regulation, the Service rules or policies, or the rights of third parties or to investigate any suspected conduct which we deem improper. Notwithstanding the prohibitions on the transfer of your personally identifiable information, We may transfer Your information in connection with a fundamental business change such as a merger, consolidation, or the sale of substantially all of our assets. We utilize third party service providers for certain functions relating to this Service who may have access to Your information. Each such third party provider has a privacy policy at least as restrictive as this Privacy Policy or has contractually agreed to fulfill all obligations provided for in this Privacy Policy through a data processing agreement or its equivalent. We and our third party service providers primarily store and process data that may contain your personally identifiable information in the United States. However, in the event of a security incident, our third party security provider may access such data from security operation centers outside of the United States.
HOW WE USE PERSONAL INFORMATION
The information We collect from you is an important part of Our ability to offer high-quality products that are relevant to You. Also, from time to time, We may ask for Your opinion or level of interest in certain products. We use this information to customize Your experience with Us and, among other things, to determine which products You would like Us to provide.WE DO NOT SELL YOUR PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION - WE USE YOUR PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION ONLY AS PERMITTED BY THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND TO IMPROVE YOUR CUSTOMER EXPERIENCE WITH US. IF YOU SUBMIT INFORMATION TO US REGARDING YOUR EXPERIENCE WITH ONE OR MORE OF OUR PRODUCTS ("YOUR TESTIMONIAL SUBMISSION"), THIS PRIVACY POLICY DOES NOT APPLY TO YOUR TESTIMONIAL SUBMISSION. INSTEAD, PLEASE SEE OUR TERMS OF USE FOR HOW WE MAY USE YOUR TESTIMONIAL SUBMISSION.
HOW WE SAFEGUARD PERSONAL INFORMATION
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of Your information, We have put in place commercially reasonable physical, electronic, and procedural procedures to safeguard and secure the information We have collected from You. However, please be aware that notwithstanding physical, electronic, and procedural procedures to website and secure the information We have collected from You, it is possible that third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications over the Internet. We limit access to Your personal information by Our employees to only those individuals who have a need to use it in the course of performing their job duties.The safety and security of your information also depend on You. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our Site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask that You not share your password with anyone.
MANAGE YOUR SECURITY SETTINGS
You may manage how your browser handles cookies and related technologies by adjusting its privacy and security settings. Browsers are different, so refer to instructions related to your browser to learn about cookie-related and other privacy and security settings that may be available. You can opt-out of being targeted by certain third-party advertising companies online by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”)’s website at http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/.You may manage how your mobile browser handles cookies and related technologies by adjusting your mobile device privacy and security settings. Please refer to instructions provided by your mobile service provider or the manufacturer of your device to learn how to adjust your settings.If you wish to opt out of receiving offers directly from Company service providers, you can follow the opt-out instructions in the emails that they send you.
THIRD PARTY COOKIES AND OTHER TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES
Some content or applications, including advertisements, on the Site, are served by third-parties, including advertisers, ad networks and servers, content providers, and application providers. These third parties may use cookies alone or in conjunction with web beacons or other tracking technologies to collect information about you when you use our Website. The information they collect may be associated with your personal information or they may collect information, including personal information, about your online activities over time and across different websites and other online services. They may use this information to provide you with interest-based (behavioral) advertising or other targeted content.We may use third parties such as network advertisers to serve advertisements on our Site and on third-party websites or other media (e.g., social networking platforms) that enable us and third parties to target advertisements to you for products and services in which you might be interested. Third-party ad network providers, advertisers, sponsors, and/or traffic measurement services may use cookies, JavaScript, web beacons (including clear GIFs), LSOs and other tracking technologies to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content to you. These third-party cookies and other technologies are governed by each third party’s specific privacy policy, not this one. We may provide these third-party advertisers with information, including personal information, about you.Users in the United States may opt out of many third-party ad networks. For example, you may go to the Digital Advertising Alliance (“DAA”) Consumer Choice Page for information about opting out of interest-based advertising and your choices regarding having information used by DAA companies. You may also go to the NAI’s Consumer Opt-Out Page for information about opting out of interest-based advertising and your choices regarding having information used by NAI members. The NAI’s main webpage is located at www.networkadvertising.org.Opting out from one or more companies listed on the DAA Consumer Choice Page or the NAI Consumer Opt-Out Page will opt you out from those companies’ delivery of interest-based content or ads to you, but it does not mean you will no longer receive any advertising through our Site or on other websites or applications. You may continue to receive advertisements, for example, based on the particular website that you are viewing (i.e., contextually based ads). Also, if your browsers are configured to reject cookies when you opt out on the DAA or NAI websites, your opt-out may not be effective. Additional information is available on the DAA’s website at www.aboutads.info or the NAI’s website.We do not control these third parties’ tracking technologies or how they may be used. If you have any questions about an advertisement or other targeted content, you should contact the responsible provider directly.
CHOICES ABOUT HOW WE USE AND DISCLOSE YOUR INFORMATION
We strive to provide you with choices regarding the Personal Information you provide to us. We have created mechanisms to provide you with the following control over your information:Tracking Technologies and Advertising: You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent. To learn how you can manage your Flash cookie settings, visit the Flash player settings page on Adobe’s website. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this Site may then be inaccessible or not function properly.Disclosure of Your Information for Third-Party Advertising: If you do not want us to share your Personal Information with unaffiliated or non-agent third parties for promotional purposes, you can opt-out by using the opt-out method. You can also always opt-out by sending us an email stating your request to optout@wingilariver.com.Promotional Offers from the Company: If you do not wish to have your email address/contact information used by us to promote our own or third parties’ products or services, you can opt-out by sending us an email stating your request to optout@wingilariver.com. If we have sent you a promotional email, you may send us a return email asking to be omitted from future email distributions. This opt-out does not apply to information provided to us as a result of a product purchase, warranty registration, product service experience, or other transactions.Targeted Advertising: If you do not want us to use information that we collect or that you provide to us to deliver advertisements according to our advertisers’ target-audience preferences, you can opt-out by contacting us at optout@wingilariver.com. For this opt-out to function, you must have your browser set to accept browser cookies. We do not control third parties’ collection or use of your information to serve interest-based advertising. However, these third parties may provide you with ways to choose not to have your information collected or used in this way. You can opt out of receiving targeted ads from members of the NAI on the website at networkadvertising.org.
RIGHTS TO ACCESS AND CONTROL YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
Any personal data that we collect is based upon your consent as detailed in this Privacy Policy. You have many choices concerning the collection, use, and sharing of your data, including the ability to:Delete Data: You may request that we delete your Personal Information. Please note that we cannot delete your Personal Information except by also deleting your user account.Change or Correct Data: You can also ask us to change, update, or fix your data in certain cases, particularly if it’s inaccurate. We may not accommodate a request to change information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect.Object to, or Limit or Restrict, Use of Data: You may request that we do not use your Personal Information, but keep in mind that this will terminate our ability to provide any Service(s) to you.Right to Access and/or Take Your Data: You can ask us for a copy of your Personal Information.You may send us an email at privacyaccess@wingilariver.com to request access to, obtain copies of, correct, or delete any Personal Information that you have provided to us.
YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS
California Civil Code Section § 1798.83 permits users of our Site that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to privacyaccess@wingilariver.com.
WE HAVE NO RESPONSIBILITY FOR LINKED WEBSITES OR SOCIAL MEDIA WEB SITES
This Service may contain links to other websites that may provide information about issues, products or services of potential interest to You or may have applications that link from social media web sites such as Facebook or Twitter. Each of these websites may have its own privacy policy governing the collection, use and distribution of information, which may be different than Our Privacy Policy. Accordingly, We do not assume responsibility for information collected, used or distributed by other persons or entities that maintain websites linked to or with this Website or any other liability whatsoever with respect to your interaction or use of these web sites. Furthermore, We do not endorse any such linked website or any products or services available at or through any such linked website.
CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY
We may change this Privacy Policy at any time; changes to this Privacy Policy shall be effective immediately upon the posting of such changes. Therefore, You should review this Privacy Policy from time to time.
CONTACTING US REGARDING YOUR PRIVACY
If you have questions or concerns about Our Privacy Policy, Our use of Your information, or if You would like to correct any of Your information in Our records please write to Us at:Gila River Casinos5040 Wild Horse Pass Blvd.P.O. Box 6790Chandler, Arizona 85246
#PLAYATGILA
For the 10th Day of Gila, we’re giving away a wi
Say hello to the 8th Day of Gila! Still need plans
This is your hand and there’s an all-in on the t
Load More...
Make sure to use the hashtag #playatgila for all your social media
and check back here to see if your posts get featured!
Gain access to exclusive perks and privileges with THE Card®. Earn and use points across all three properties plus participating partners.
More Details
SIGN UP FOR EXCLUSIVE OFFERS & NEWS
SIGN ME UP
SIGN UP FOR EXCLUSIVE OFFERS & NEWS
SIGN ME UP
1.800.946.4452
INQUIRIES
INQUIRIES
Hotel Policies
©2020 Gila River Hotels & Casinos Owned and operated by the Gila River Indian Community. If you are 21 or older, we invite you to explore our website. Please Play Responsibly. If you have a gambling problem, please call 1-800-639-8783.
Close
DISCOUNTS + TERMS
Discounts
$10 off for GRIC members (enrollment card required), Group Sales and Hotel Sales Package
clients and GRGE Team Members.
Gila River Casinos Players Club card members receive the following discounts based on tier
level Emerald $5, Ruby $10, Gold $15, Platinum $20. All discounts are per ticket, 4 tickets
maximum per Players Club member. Tickets are at retail pricing when purchased online or by
phone. Discounts are available at the Box Office only.
Terms
All Guests under 21 must be accompanied by a ticketed adult 21 or older.
Additional taxes and fees may be added at checkout. Prices subject to change. All sales are
final. No refunds or exchanges.
NEED HELP? CONTACT US
Close
Thank You.
Your Message Has Been Sent.
In your email, please include:
Your Name
Player's Club number (if available)
Time Range
Indicate if you want a Win/Loss Statement(s) and/or tax forms
Your contact information
Request In-Person
Complete a Request form for your Win/Loss Statement and/or Tax Form at the Players Club.
Players Club can generate Win/Loss Statements for you.
If you are requesting copies of your tax forms, fill out the form and then
send it to Revenue Audit to process.
Request By Phone
Call Camilla Benally at800-946-4452 ext 1998 Monday
- Friday, 7:30AM - 3:30PM
Please note that it can take up to three days for a response
